okay all right okay it was a bit of a
好的，好的，有点
bit of a bumpy start I think we're on
我开始有点坎start
the right track and so if you're joining
正确的轨道，所以如果您要加入
us from anywhere around the world thanks
我们来自世界各地
for joining our stream and we're a
加入我们的信息流，我们是
little late here but I'm glad we got a
这里有点晚，但我很高兴我们得到了
chance to get started I'm joined today
机会开始，我今天加入了
by my colleague and friend Andre
由我的同事和朋友安德烈
chepstow he's joining us from Moscow
chepstow他从莫斯科加入我们
right now and today we're going to
现在和今天，我们将
demonstrate some cool new features
展示一些很棒的新功能
inside IntelliJ IDEA 14 specifically
专门在IntelliJ IDEA 14中
related to GWT tool chain and we've
与GWT工具链有关，我们已经
introduced improved support for that in
引入了对此的改进支持
IntelliJ IDEA 14 so he will demonstrate
IntelliJ IDEA 14，他将演示
how to use and set up a web toolkit for
如何使用和设置Web工​​具包
application and and debug it using the
应用程序并使用
visual debug the super dev mode in
视觉调试超级开发模式
Google web toolkit so the first thing
Google Web工具包，所以第一件事
you'll need to do when you open a new
打开新书时需要做的
project is you'll create a sample
项目是您将创建一个示例
application inside the new project
新项目中的应用程序
wizard here so I'll select the Google
向导在这里，所以我将选择Google
web toolkit model from my projects here
我的项目中的Web工具箱模型
and you have to make sure to use a
而且您必须确保使用
recent distribution of the Google web
最近发布的Google网站
toolkit or a quick application so here
工具包或快速应用程序，所以在这里
we're using two point six point one and
我们使用两点六点一
that's the most recent one that includes
这是最新的，包括
the super dev mode enabled so we'll show
启用了超级开发模式，因此我们将显示
that off now
那现在
I just created a simple hello world of
我刚刚创建了一个简单的
wit application so I'll just walk
机智的应用程序，所以我就走
through that one more time will create a
通过那一次，将创造一个
new project in order to get started
新项目以开始
using a super dev mode on IntelliJ IDEA
在IntelliJ IDEA上使用超级开发模式
14 we'll create a new application so
14我们将创建一个新的应用程序
we'll go down again to our google web
我们将再次进入我们的谷歌网站
toolkit model here and just remember to
工具箱模型，请记住
select the two point six point one
选择两点六点一
distribution if you don't have that on
分配，如果你没有
there should be a little download link
应该有一个小下载链接
here that you can go to the quit project
在这里你可以去退出项目
site and download that those sources so
网站并下载这些资源，以便
you can well create a sample application
您可以很好地创建一个示例应用程序
here and we'll click Next and we'll just
在这里，我们将单击下一步，我们将
call this hello
叫你好
quick okay we'll finish up here and then
很快好吧，我们将在这里结束，然后
IntelliJ IDEA will create all our our
IntelliJ IDEA将创造我们所有的
project files and its own model and then
项目文件及其自己的模型，然后
once this gets started we'll be able to
一旦开始，我们将能够
demonstrate how this all works so so so
展示一切如何运作
good is a project that allows you to
一个好的项目，可以让您
write all your your client-server
写下您所有的客户服务器
applications using Java and with
使用Java和
JavaScript in the front end so it
前端有JavaScript
compiles to to JavaScript and and we'll
编译为JavaScript，我们将
show example of how that works so here
在这里显示如何工作的示例
in our source folder we have some client
在我们的源文件夹中，我们有一些客户端
application code and some server code
应用程序代码和一些服务器代码
that goes along with our application
与我们的应用程序一起
this is just a simple application it
这只是一个简单的应用程序
it displays hello from the client and
它从客户端显示问候
then the server says hello and so forth
然后服务器说你好，依此类推
so we'll just we'll change this here so
所以我们只是要在这里更改它
this is my client application code and I
这是我的客户端应用程序代码，我
can create some new code say I'd say
可以创建一些新的代码，比如说
hello server and so and then we have the
你好服务器，等等，然后我们有
server will say hello client and will
服务器将打招呼客户端，并会
reply
回复
okay and we're running off on Tomcat 8
好的，我们在Tomcat 8上运行
point 0.5 but you can use whatever
点0.5，但您可以使用任何东西
application server you're most
您最需要的应用服务器
comfortable with
适应
so first things first I'll need to add
所以首先我需要添加
it my run configuration in order to get
它是我的运行配置，以便获得
this to run and what I want to do in
这要运行，我想在其中做什么
order to use the new GWT functionality
为了使用新的GWT功能
super dev mode in IntelliJ 14 you'll
IntelliJ 14中的超级开发模式
just enable this use super dev mode
只需启用此使用超级开发模式
checkbox here and if you'd like to use
此处的复选框，以及是否要使用
the JavaScript debugger alongside that
JavaScript调试器
you can select that and then I'll select
您可以选择它，然后我将选择
Chrome browser because I have a plugin
Chrome浏览器，因为我有一个插件
installed in Chrome that will allow me
安装在Chrome中，可以让我
to talk to my IDE and and get all that
与我的IDE交谈并获得所有
in sync so if you have any additional
同步，所以如果您还有其他
dev mode parameters that you like to
您想要的开发模式参数
feed in say like a configuration port or
像配置端口那样输入
an address that you'd like to bind to
您想绑定到的地址
this application then you can set that
该应用程序，然后您可以设置
right there and then we'll click apply
就在那，然后我们点击“应用”
so this should be all configured
所以应该全部配置好
correctly now and now in order to run
现在正确地运行
this application we'll just click run or
在此应用程序中，我们只需单击运行或
we can press shift f10
我们可以按Shift F10
control-shift-n let's try that I will
Control-Shift-N让我们尝试一下
click the Run button here and so what
单击此处的“运行”按钮等等
that will do is it will compile all the
那会做的就是编译所有
applications sources and and this will
应用程序源，这将
open up an instance of our browser so
打开我们的浏览器实例
you can immediately start interacting
您可以立即开始互动
with our application and and debugging
与我们的应用程序和调试
it and so forth so you'll remember that
等等，所以您会记住
I've enabled the JavaScript debugger now
我已经启用了JavaScript调试器
once this gets started it should start
一旦开始，就应该开始
up the the the run application here and
在这里运行应用程序
so it's it's running on GWT 2.6 and
因此它正在GWT 2.6和
we'll just wait a few moments here so it
我们在这里等一下
should start up momentarily okay so the
应该会暂时启动，这样
code server is ready and with this which
代码服务器已准备就绪，与此相关
should do if I've configured it
如果我已经配置了该怎么办
correctly is you'll see it will ping my
正确，您会看到它会ping我的
browser here and I just I don't have to
浏览器在这里，我只是不必
really do anything I can just go over to
真的可以做任何我可以去做的事情
the browser and it's compiled my simple
浏览器并将其编译为我的简单
application right now and you'll notice
现在申请，您会注意到
that I have a JetBrains IDE support
我有JetBrains IDE支持
plugin for Chrome this is connected to
Chrome的插件已连接到
intelligent idea and this will allow me
聪明的主意，这将使我
to debug the application from within my
从我的内部调试应用程序
IDE and it'll connect the JavaScript so
IDE，它将连接JavaScript，因此
that I can read all the this to the
我可以读到所有这些
correct stack frame and related
正确的堆栈框架及相关
information so this is just our sample
信息，所以这只是我们的示例
application it should work like we
应用程序应该像我们一样工作
described hello server hello client and
描述了你好服务器你好客户端和
and this is running again on on the on
这又在继续运行
the browser from from the client and the
来自客户端和浏览器的浏览器
server is running from intelligent idea
服务器从聪明的想法运行
right off I'm cat and so if we set a
我是猫，所以如果我们设置一个
breakpoint since we since we're using
断点，因为我们自从使用
the JavaScript debugger right now if we
如果我们现在使用JavaScript调试器
set a breakpoint in the client-side code
在客户端代码中设置断点
for example let's just put a breakpoint
例如让我们放一个断点
right there and we rerun this
就在那里，我们重新运行
application so we click it again we've
应用程序，因此我们再次单击它
paused in the debugger right and
暂停在调试器中，然后
resume this inside the browser if you'd
如果愿意，可以在浏览器中恢复
like or you can jump over to your IDE
喜欢，或者您可以跳到您的IDE
which is somewhere here I'll minimize
在这里我将最小化
this and you can see that should just be
这个，你可以看到应该是
a moment here you can it'll it'll be
一会儿在这里你可以
paused at that exact line in my IDE
在我的IDE中停在了该行
right and if I go to the debugger
对，如果我去调试器
and it looks like it's frozen right now
好像现在已经冻结了
but if I go to my debugger I will be
但是如果我去调试器，我会
able to see the all the specs ok so it
能够看到所有规格都可以
looks like it works now if we if we
如果我们
inspect some of these variable you can
检查其中一些变量，您可以
see that this is all this is all
看到这就是全部
JavaScript right and and these
JavaScript对，这些
correspond to what's running on the
对应于正在运行的
client and so you should be able to see
客户，因此您应该能够看到
some of those JavaScript files inside
其中一些JavaScript文件
let's see if we can find those files ok
让我们看看是否可以找到这些文件
well if not let's just move on to the
好吧，如果没有，让我们继续前进
next part so let's say you want to debug
下一部分，假设您要调试
your client-side application and your
您的客户端应用程序和您的
server-side at the same time right so
服务器端在同一时间对
right now since we're not running any
现在，因为我们没有运行任何
any server-side debugger in our in our
我们的任何服务器端调试器
IDE right now then we'll we'll just
IDE，现在，我们将
resume this here and you can see that
在这里恢复，您可以看到
it'll resume it in a debugger here in
它将在这里的调试器中恢复
the IDE as well so they're both
IDE也是如此
connected and we'll so so let's say we'd
连接，所以我们会说，我们会
like to make make a modification to our
想对我们的产品进行修改
client-side code right so let's just
客户端代码正确，让我们就
demonstrate that
证明
so we'll add on clients here okay and
所以我们会在这里添加客户
now what we'll do is we'll save that and
现在我们要做的就是保存
well click on this EV mode on a bookmark
并在书签上单击此EV模式
on my bookmarks bar here so I'll click
在我的书签栏上，所以我将点击
that and I can choose a module to
那我可以选择一个模块
recompile
重新编译
so I'll click recompile this and you can
所以我将点击“重新编译”，您可以
does that so that's a little bit of
这样做是为了
JavaScript that programmatically reloads
以编程方式重新加载的JavaScript
your your modified sources so again this
您修改过的资源，因此再次
is paused and if we resume this you can
已暂停，如果我们继续执行此操作，则可以
see my new client side implementation
看到我新的客户端实现
here in Java right
Java在这里
so all you need to do is save your
所以您要做的就是保存您的
JavaScript your Java code and then
用JavaScript编写Java代码，然后
reload that from the browser here using
使用以下命令从浏览器重新加载
this dead load bookmark and I think you
这个空载书签，我想你
can find that inside if you just slowed
可以放慢速度在里面找到
up application here you could change the
在这里，您可以更改
DM C it's go to the other directory so
DM C转到另一个目录，所以
this directory here and you should be
这个目录在这里，你应该是
able to drag this to your your bookmarks
能够将其拖到您的书签中
bar from the the super dev mode
超级开发模式下的酒吧
application here in the browser I can't
我无法在浏览器中找到应用程序
find that right now but if you look on
现在找到那个，但是如果你继续看
the documentation on the project website
项目网站上的文档
and you should be able to find that
而且您应该能够找到
previously and if you look at the URL
以前，如果您查看网址
it's just a bit of programmatic
这只是程序化的一点
JavaScript reload that that content
JavaScript重新加载该内容
right okay so let's let's move on so
好吧，让我们继续前进
we'll go back to our application here
我们将在这里返回到我们的应用程序
and we'll just cancel this and we'll
我们将取消它，我们将
stop it okay and now I'd like to debug
停止吧，现在我要调试
my server at the same time right so I've
我的服务器在同一时间，所以我已经
set a breakpoint here on the the server
在服务器上的此处设置断点
implementation of this right and I'll
实施这项权利，我会
just click debug here and I'll debug
只需单击“调试”，我将进行调试
this application and I better make sure
这个应用程序，我最好确保
that that this is not running right now
那个现在没有运行
because this uses this port right so
因为这正确使用了这个端口
we'll stop this as well and we'll debug
我们也会停止此操作，并进行调试
that again so if the port is already
再说一遍，如果端口已经
bound then you
束缚你
you have to make sure to unbind that
您必须确保取消绑定
court and that it should work again so
法院，它应该再次工作，这样
it looks like the code is ready right
看起来代码已经准备好了
okay so now I'm going to show you
好吧，现在我要告诉你
something really I think it's just it's
真的，我认为只是
I I really like this feature so there's
我真的很喜欢这个功能，所以
something that allows you to as you're
可以让你像你一样的东西
debugging your your server-side code
调试您的服务器端代码
this is all being run Java bytecode on
这都是在Java字节码上运行的
the the war now on top of Tomcat but you
现在是Tomcat之上的战争，但是您
can reload this using using hot-swap so
可以使用热插拔来重新加载
so let's say you make a change to your
因此，假设您对自己的产品进行了更改
code but first let's show how this works
代码，但首先让我们展示一下它是如何工作的
right okay so it's paused so this is
好的，所以它已暂停，所以这是
this is the blindside breakpoint that
这是盲目的断点
we've set right so we'll resume that
我们已经设置正确，因此我们将继续
right okay and now we've hit the second
好吧，现在我们击中了第二个
breakpoint on our server okay so this is
我们服务器上的断点好吧，这是
this is this is stopped right here and
这是这里就停止了
you can see all the stack frames and
您可以看到所有堆栈帧和
this is again this is um this is Java
这又是这个，这是Java
bytecode right okay so you can you can
正确的字节码，这样您就可以
stop there and so it's about to display
停在那里，所以它将显示
this message right so if we click f9 or
该消息正确，所以如果我们单击f9或
we resume this program right and then
我们马上恢复该程序，然后
you go back to the cert of the browser
您返回浏览器的证书
you can see that it jumps right back so
你可以看到它跳回来了
this is this is actually a live
这实际上是现场直播
interaction it's going from the client
互动来自客户
to the server and then we can resume the
到服务器，然后我们可以继续
server since it's paused and you can see
服务器，因为它已暂停，您可以看到
that the result here I'll just try that
结果在这里我会尝试
one more time right so if we click this
再等一次，如果我们单击此
it's paused in the debugger right this
它在调试器中暂停了
is the client-side JavaScript
是客户端JavaScript
implementation will resume this jump
实施将恢复此跳转
over to our IDE and then resume this
转到我们的IDE，然后继续
again and you can see it's displayed ok
再次，您可以看到它显示正常
so now I'll show you how hot swapping
所以现在我将向您展示如何进行热插拔
works so let's say you you'd like to
起作用，所以假设您要
modify your server-side code um right
修改您的服务器端代码um
and so let's let's let's do both at the
因此，让我们让我们在
same time just so we won't reload
同时，这样我们就不会重新加载
anything like this right we'll just save
像这样的权利，我们将保存
it and then it'll be recompiled
它，然后将重新编译
and then we can we can you can see the
然后我们可以，我们可以看到
changes
变化
okay so our client will say this or it
好吧，我们的客户会说这句话
let's let's let's try okay so that's
让我们让我们尝试好吧，那是
that's fine okay and then and we'll jump
很好，然后我们会跳
over to our server right and then we'll
转到我们的服务器上，然后我们将
we'll go over a server and the server
我们将遍历服务器和服务器
will say
会说
okay okay so all we just do is save this
好吧好吧，所以我们要做的就是保存此
again right and then we'll make sure
再次正确，然后我们将确保
that that's that's being recompiled so
那就是被重新编译，所以
you can you can recompile that by
您可以通过以下方式重新编译
pressing ctrl shift F nine and they'll
按ctrl shift F九，他们将
compile this back in and just make sure
编译回去并确保
that you have hot code hot swapping
您有热代码热插拔
enabled so if you go to the debugger in
已启用，因此如果您进入调试器
your settings right you'll have to
您必须正确设置
enable hot swap and just just make sure
启用热插拔，只需确保
that it reloads those classes in the
它会重新加载这些类
background always because that's a good
背景总是因为这很好
thing to have right okay so we won't
事情还好吧，所以我们不会
touch anything now we won't you won't
现在触摸任何东西，我们不会，您不会
reload the application right we'll jump
重新加载应用程序，我们将跳转
back to our browser here and and we'll
回到此处的浏览器，我们将
just we'll just reload the the
只是我们将重新加载
client-side code from our browser right
来自我们浏览器的客户端代码
so we'll compile that and we'll click it
所以我们将其编译，然后单击它
once more okay so as usual you'll see
再一次好吧，像往常一样，你会看到
the the pause in the JavaScript side
JavaScript端的暂停
again if you jump back here you'll see
再一次，如果你跳回到这里，你会看到
that on the JavaScript debugger it
在JavaScript调试器上
should should be paused right at that
应该在那儿停下来
point right so it will either resume it
指向正确，因此它将恢复
here or will zoom it from the the
在这里或将其放大
browser and then we'll jump back to our
浏览器，然后我们将跳回到我们的
IDE and you can see that again it's
IDE，您可以再次看到它是
paused at this line right and then we'll
在此行暂停，然后我们将
resume this by pressing f9 and you can
通过按f9继续操作，您可以
see right here in the browser that the
在浏览器中看到的是
new server-side code has been hot
新的服务器端代码一直很热门
swapped in and you can you can you can
交换，你可以你可以
do that really quickly right so this is
真的很快就做到了，所以这是
this is a way to really improve your
这是一种真正改善您的方式
your productivity when you're developing
开发时的生产力
these applications because the LifeSite
这些应用程序是因为LifeSite
you know you don't have to recompile the
您知道您不必重新编译
whole thing so this is a huge
整个事情，所以这是一个巨大的
application
应用
may take 10 minutes to recompile right
可能需要10分钟才能重新编译正确
so you just want to compile those
所以你只想编译那些
classes that have changed and then
发生变化的课程，然后
that'll hot-swap it right back in and
可以立即将其热插拔，
you can do this both on the client and
您可以在客户端和
on the server so this is a really
在服务器上，所以这真的是
powerful way to use to use super dev
使用超级开发工具的强大方法
mode in quit Sixpoint the latest version
模式退出Sixpoint最新版本
who quit and IntelliJ IDEA 14 they both
谁退出和IntelliJ IDEA 14他们俩
support these features and so now I
支持这些功能，所以现在我
think I think having to recompile your
认为我认为必须重新编译您的
whole application will be a thing of the
整个应用程序将成为
past this is this is this is really cool
过去这就是这真的很酷
okay yeah so I think um I think that's
好的，是的，所以我认为我是
that's that's a good place to just out
那是一个出去的好地方
what would you like to let's see so
您想看什么
would you like to just to show now I
你想现在显示我吗
think I think we've gone over the basic
认为我认为我们已经超越了基本
functionality and the debugger just just
功能和调试器只是
make sure that you used the JetBrains
确保您使用了JetBrains
the latest version of the jet planes
最新版本的喷气式飞机
plugin for for Chrome and if that
适用于Chrome的插件，如果有的话
doesn't work I should I should mention
不起作用，我应该提到
so so your IDE is is listening on a
所以您的IDE正在监听
certain port right so you may have to
某些端口正确，因此您可能必须
configure that's under options so you
在选项下配置
just make sure that that the that the
只需确保该
it's listening on the same port and an
在同一端口上监听
address as as the IDE is it is looking
如IDE一样寻找地址
for so so this will connect to the ID on
为此，它将连接到ID
this port right and it should detect it
这个端口正确，它应该检测到它
but if not then you just have to enter
但是如果没有，那么您只需要输入
it manually right and again you can find
它手动正确，一次又一次，您可以找到
that here in your your dev mode console
在您的开发人员模式控制台中
by going to let's see so it should say
通过去看看，所以它应该说
when it starts up see we'll go to run
当它启动时，我们将运行
here
这里
which port that's broadcasting on
在哪个端口上广播
so it starts jetty on this this port
所以它开始在这个港口跳船
right and you can configure that but see
正确，您可以配置它，但请参阅
we can phone but anyway just just make
我们可以打电话，但无论如何
sure that it's all set up
确保一切都已设置
okay so so that's all I wanted to share
好，所以这就是我要分享的全部
with you today thanks for joining us and
今天与您一起感谢您加入我们
thanks Andre for for proposing this this
感谢安德烈（Andre）提出这个建议
hangout I think I think this is um it
视讯聚会我想我觉得这很好
was there was a little bumpy at first
起初有点颠簸吗
but I'm glad I'm glad we got it sorted
但我很高兴我很高兴我们把它整理好了
out
出